dinstudio.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy policy

This is Din Studio Sverige AB’s (" **Din Studio** ") privacy policy for processing of your personal data and other information that we might collect when you visit our webpage. This privacy policy is included in Din Studio’s user terms for this webpage. By using this webpage you accept our privacy policy. If you do not accept the privacy policy you shall not use the webpage. Din Studio might change the content of this privacy policy from time to time. Therefore, you should check this information on a regular basis to see if the policy has been amended. If you continue to use this webpage after amendments of the policy have been published, you are deemed to have accepted the amendments.

### Information we collect

Every time you visit Din Studio’s webpage, Din Studio automatically collects the following information:

  * Your IP address
  * The name and version of your browser
  * Your operating system
  * Information regarding which webpage you visited just before our webpage
  * Date and time

### Use of information

The information is used statistically in order to analyze how the webpage is used. What we investigate is among other things the number of visitors, how they found us, how they navigate on the website and what time of day the webpage has the most visitors. Furthermore, we investigate certain regional information, from what webpages the visitors comes and search keys that visitors have used to locate the website. This information is used in-house within Din Studio in order to measure the result of marketing operations and offer a better service to our customers.

Din Studio cares about your personal integrity. Naturally, we are in compliance with current legislation regarding [EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)](https://www.eugdpr.org/), to protect your integrity. Only a limited amount of persons with certain authorization have access to the information.

Din Studio will not transfer your personal data, like address, telephone number or e-mail address to any third party.

### Cookies

We use so-called _cookies_ on our webpage. According to the Swedish Act on Electronic Communication (2003:389) everyone who visits a webpage with cookies shall receive information on:

  * That the webpage includes cookies
  * What those cookies are used for
  * How cookies can be avoided

Cookies are small information files that are saved by the browser on the computer hard disk. The cookies that are used on our webpage are among other things used to identify whether it is the first time a person visits the webpage or if it has happened before and to what account you have chosen to log in when you as a customer log in to access your webpage. A cookie does not for example tell us about a visitor's e-mail address and we cannot use it to get any other information about you. It is possible to configure your browser if you want it to block cookies or if you want to receive information every time a cookie is sent. Such a choice might however entail that you cannot use our webpage or part of it properly. Previously saved cookies can be deleted through the browser. Please see the browser's help pages for more information.
